### KATARZYNA SOCHON

# HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATIONS

Over 6 years of experience in customer service field

Effective communicator, attentive listener, patient and diplomatic

Highly skilled in representing employer intelligently and professionally

Sincerely enjoy working with people, in person and over the phone

Good sense of humor

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### **CUSTOMER SERIVE REPRESENTATIVE, BLIZZARD ENTERTAINMENT, CORK**

August 2009-present

#### **Responsibilities and Achievements:**

Daily duties include dealing with our customers concerns with our products either within the games we develop or externally with billing and technical issues for their accounts.

- CTIOS new phone system pilot testing.

Testing new system before old one was replaced. That included testing functionality and reporting problems that arose.

Recording prompts for customers and crisis messages.

Launch of polish support

Flexible approach with schedule assignments and shift to accommodate polish support in first days of going live for customers with Sc2 launch

- Assisting with suicide cases -polish customers.

That involve contacting police and following up on a case with appropriate reporting.

#### CUSTOMER SERIVE REPRESENTATIVE- COMPLAINT DEPARTMENT, ABTRAN, CORK

March 2009-August 2009

#### **Responsibilities and Achievements:**

Customer assistance and support with billing and account issues as also complaint branch for legal department.

 Within a month of starting job I was moved to complaint branch of support that is responsible for outbound calls to customers informing them of actions taken and reporting to legal department

#### ASSISTANT MANAGER, BODEGA, CORK

May 2007-January 2009

#### **Responsibilities and Achievements:**

Scheduling staff and assigning to tasks, money handling and counting, stock ordering and counting, interviews, opening and closing up the club. Cooperating with security to insure staff and customer's safety.

- Supervising Summer solstice opening event

Confirming all involved parties confirm their attendance. Assisting with all acts logistics-music, lights and performance safety. Organizing transport and guiding to place if necessary.

Organising UCC Next Top Model charity event.

Organizing and overlooking whole event starting with food, light, music, stage preparations, adverts in local newspapers and throughout posters.

#### RESERVATIONS AGENT, STARWOOD HOTELS AND RESORT, CORK CITY

June 2007- December 2007

Customer satisfaction team assisting with hotel reservation. Reception duties.

- VIP concierge

Reservation of hotel rooms for VIP guests and making sure that all requests of guest are organized for example flowers, choice of bed lining, trips and transport for guest

Page | 2 Kasia Sochon

#### - Reception

Answering calls with enquiries, making sure that office guest book is up to date, assisting with accommodating new hires. Responsible for employee attendance list print out in case of emergency and evacuation. Reporting all technical issues to facility manager.

## VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

**Hope for Home- Animal Shelter- Katowice-** 1999-2000

Help with cats and dogs, feeding, grooming, cleaning and walks

Cordis Hospice- Katowice- 2001

As trained nurse I was able to make pain relief injections and overall care, but what was most important for patients is presence and company of other people in that difficult time for them.

The sexual Health center- Cork- present

Help with bookkeeping and any every day enquires through email and phone.

**SKILLS** 

MSOffice certificate – that include Word, Excel and Excel for Business

**First Aid Course**- Level 5 FETAC certificate Bookkeeping and Accountant – Leaving cert

**EDUCATION** 

MASTER OF ARTS- PR AND COMMUNICATION, UNIVERISTY OF SILESIA, POLAND, 2007 MEDICAL SCHOOL, NURSERY FACULTY, POLAND, 2001

LEAVING CERT, POLAND, 1999

Page | 3 Kasia Sochon